The Yale School of Music Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Programs, Series III
  - Jan 1955-July 1955 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Aug 1955-Dec 1955 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Jan 1956-June, 10, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - June 26, 1956-Dec 1956 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Jan 1957-Apr 17, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Apr 18, 1957-Dec 1957 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Jan 1958-Apr 1958 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - May 1958-Dec 1958 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Jan 1959-Apr 1959 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - May 1959-Dec 1959 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Jan 1960-Apr 1960 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - May 1960-Dec 1960 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Jan 1961-Apr 1961 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - May 1961-Dec 1961 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Jan 1962-Apr 1962 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - May 1962-Dec 1962 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Jan 1963-Apr 1963 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - May 1963-Dec 1963 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Jan 1964-Apr 1964 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - May 1964-Dec 1964 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Jan 1965-Apr 21, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Apr 22, 1965-Sept 1965 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Oct 1965-Dec 1965 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Jan 1966-Apr 1966 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - May 1966-Nov 9,1966 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Nov 11, 1966-Mar 1967 (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Apr 1967-Oct 1967 (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Nov 1967-Dec 1967 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Jan 1968-Mar 1968 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Apr 1968-Oct 1968 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Nov 1968-Dec 1968 (Box 14, Folder 81)
  - Jan 1969-Mar 1969 (Box 14, Folder 82)
  - Apr 1969-May 1969 (Box 14, Folder 83)
  - June 1969-Dec 1969 (Box 14, Folder 84)
  - Jan 1970-Feb 1970 (Box 14, Folder 85)
  - Mar 1970-June 1970 (Box 14, Folder 86)
  - Chamber Music, Faculty Series, 1929-1939 (Box A)
  - University Glee Club, 1924-1944 (Box B)
  - Index
    This index lists the major program series and the number of programs within that series for each year. Special programs not in series are also listed. Faculty recitals and student recitals are not listed. Unless otherwise indicated by a number in parentheses, there is one program per year listed.
    - 15th through 18th centuries: Program of music from, 1968
    - Aguilars, 1933
    - Albert Arnold Sprague Chamber Concerts, 1921 (2), 1922 (3), 1923 (2), 1924 (4), 1925 (2), 1926 (3), 1927 (3), 1928 (3), 1929 (2), 1930 (4), 1931 (1), 1932 (3), 1933 (3), 1934 (3), 1935 (3), 1936 (3), 1938 (2), 1937 (1)
    - Alumni Day Concert, 1959, 1960, 1961, 1962, 1964, 1966
    - American Association of University Women, New Haven Chapter and San Carlo Opera Co., 1939
    - Annual Prize Competition in Organ Playing, 1905, 1913, 1915, 1916, 1917, 1918, 1919, 1920, 1921, 1922, 1923, 1924, 1925, 1926, 1927, 1928, 1930, 1931, 1932
    - Apollo Singing Society, 1919
    - Aus der Ohe, Adele, 1905
    - Bach, J.S. - Program of the Works of, 1932
    - Beethoven Centenary, 1927
    - Berkeley Dramat, 1967
    - Berkshire Playhouse Trio, 1927 (3), 1928 (2), 1929 (3)
    - Bispham, David, 1914
    - Boston Symphony Orchestra, 1905, 1910, 1912 (2), 1917, 1921, 1922, 1923, 1926 (2), 1927 (2), 1929, 1930, 193 1, 1932, 1933 (2), 1934 (2), 1935 (2), 1936 (2), 1937 (2), 1938 (2), 1939 (2), 1940 (2), 1941 (2), 1942 (2), 1943 (2)
    - Boulanger, Nadia, 1962
    - Brahms, Johannes - Centenary of the Birth of, 1933
    - Branford-Pierson Concert Series, 1958, 1959 (2), 1960, 1961 (2), 1962 (4), 1963
    - Byrd, William - Pundit Concert in Celebration of the Tercenary of, 1924
    - Calhoun College, 1966
    - Campanari, Guiseppe, 1906
    - Cheatham, Kitty, 1914
    - Choral Art Choir, 1918 (2), 1919
    - Choral Concerts, 1916
    - Cincinnati Symphony Orchestra, 1917
    - Civic Orchestra Association of New Haven, Inc., 1935, 1936
    - Cleveland Orchestra, 1923, 1924
    - Collegium Musicum, 1951, 1960, 1961 (2), 1962 (4), 1963 (2), 1964, 1965 (2), 1966 (1), 1967, 1968
    - Commencement Concert, 1923-1954
    - Combs, Laura (solo), 30 Mar 1909
    - Connecticut State Federation of Music Clubs and Department of Music in Religious Education, 1939
    - Connecticut Swedish Singers, 1923, 1924
    - Curtis Institute of Music - Company of the Department of Opera (at Jonathan Edwards College), 1967
    - Dave Brubeck Quartet, 1956
    - Dessoff Choirs, 1948
    - Dockstader, Lew (aviator), 19 Feb 19 10
    - Elizabethan Club Presents..., 1933, 1958, 1959
    - Elizabethan Music - Concert of, 1954
    - Enesco, Georges, 1932
    - English Consort of Viols, 1962
    - English Singers, 1926, 1928, 1929, 1930
    - Expositions of Classical and Modem Chamber Music, 1909-1910 (3), 1910-1911 (2), 1911-1912 (3), 1912-1913 (4); 1913-1914 (1), 1914-1915 (5), 1916-1917 (3), 1917-1918 (5), 1918-1919 (5); 1919-1920 (5), 1920-1921 (6), 1921-1922 (5), 1922-1923 (5); 1923-1924 (5), 1924-1925 (5), 1925-1926 (4), 1926-1927 (5), 1927-1928 (5), 1928-1929 (5), 1929-1930 (5)
    - Ezra Stiles College, 1969
    - Faye Musical Society, 1926
    - Festival of Seventeenth and Eighteenth Century Music, 1939
    - Flonzaley Quartet, 1923, 1925, 1928
    - Franck - Centenary of the Birth of, 1932
    - Fremstad, Olive (singer), 24 March 1909
    - Golden Age Singers of London, 1956
    - Greater New Haven High School Choral Music Festival, 1949
    - Hamden Music Club Chorus, 1941
    - Haydn, Franz Josef - Bi-Centenary of, 1932
    - Homer, Louise, 1906, 1911
    - Horatio Parker Choir, 1921, 1922, 1923, 1924, 1925 (2), 1926
    - Hudson, Caroline (solo), 7 Dec 1909
    - Hyperion Theatre, 2/1910
    - International Student Center, 1964
    - Ives, Charles E. - Music of, 1956
    - Jonathan Edwards College - Robert C. Bates Memorial Fund, and the Friends of Music at Yale, 1967
    - Kedroff Quartet, 1929
    - Kreisler, Fritz, 24 Feb 1909, 1915
    - Lener String Quartet, 1929
    - Lenox Quartet, 1927, 1928
    - Mahler, Gustav, 23 Feb 1910
    - Manning, John C. (piano-lecture), 16 Mar 1910
    - Mazier, Eddie (comic) and His Minstrels, 19 Feb 1910
    - M.I.T. Concert Band, 1964
    - McCormack, John, 1911, 1913
    - Monteverdi, Claudio - 300th Anniversary of the Death of, 1943
    - Mozart - 150th Anniversary Celebration by the Pundits, 1941
    - Mozarteurn Orchestra of Salzburg, 1956
    - Nazimova, Madame, 15-16 Feb 1910
    - Neighborhood Music School Annual Scholarship Benefit Concert, 1960
    - New English Singers, 1932, 1934, 1936
    - New Haven - Annual Music Week, 1924 (3), 1925 (8), 1926 (5), 1928, 1929 (2), 1930, 1932 (2), 1934, 1935, 1936, 1939, 1940, 1941, 1946
    - New Haven E.R.A. Music Committee, 1935
    - New Haven Opera Society, 1965 (2), 1966 (2), 1967
    - New Haven Oratorio Society, 1905 (2), 1906 (2) 1907 (2), 1908 (2), 1909, 1910, 1912, 1913 (2)
    - New Haven Oratorio Society, 1911
    - New Haven (People's) Choral Union, 1905, 1906, 1907, 1909-1913
    - New Haven School of Music, 1910/11 (bulletin of courses)
    - New Haven String Orchestra, 1910, 1912, 1913, 1918
    - New Haven Symphony Orchestra, 1907, 1908 (5-6?), 1909 (3-5?), 1910 (2-3?), 1911, 1924 (2); 1925 (4), 1926 (2), 1936 (4), 1937 (3), 1938 (3), 1939, 1940 (3), 1941 (3), 1942 (4), 1943 (3), 1944 (3), 1945 (4); 1946 (3), 1947 (2), 1949 (3), 1950 (2), 1951 (3), 1952 (3), 1953 (3), 1954 (4), 1955, 1956 (3), 1957 (4), 1958 (4), 1959 (2); 1960 (3), 1961, 1962, 1965 (4), 1966 (2), 1967 (2), 1968 (4), 1969 (2)
    - New York Chamber Music Society, 1919, 1920
    - New York Pro Musica, 1970
    - New York Symphony, 24 Mar 1909, 16 Mar 1910, 1913 (3)
    - Ohrstrom, Knut, 1926
    - Oistrakh, David, 1955
    - Oratorio, The Seasons - sung by students fron New Haven High Schools, 1925
    - Organ Recitals, 1887, 1898 (2), 1899 (2), 1900 (4), 1903 (2), 1904 (10), 1905 (15), 1906 (9), 1908 (2), 1909 (7), 1910 (12), 1911 (13), 1912 (7), 1913 (18), 1914 (6), 1915 (8), 1916 (2), 1917 (11), 1918 (2), 1919 (6); 1920 (9), 1921 (15), 1922 (13), 1923 (13), 1924 (12), 1925 (11), 1926 (10), 1927 (10), 1928 (10), 1929 (1), 1930 (11), 1931 (12), 1932 (7), 1933 (12), 1934 (8), 1935 (8), 1936 (8); 1936-1937 (1), 1937 (8), 1938 (8), 1939 (8), 1940 (11), 1941 (6), 1942 (11), 1943 (8), 1944 (3), 1945 (7), 1946 (6), 1947 (8), 1948 (8), 1949 (11)
    - Parker, Horatio - Memorial Fund Concert, 1921
    - Paulist Choristers, 1922
    - Philharmonic Society of New York, 1910 (2), 1912 (2), 1914, 1917 (2), 1918 (2), 1919, 1920, 1921, 1922 (2), 1923 (2), 1924, 1926
    - Pops, 1945, 1946, 1947 (4), 1948 (4), 1951 (6), 1953 (5), 1954 (6), 1955 (6), 1956 (6), 1967
    - Prakavali Dancers of Thailand with the Pi-Phat Orchestra 1962
    - Pro Arte-Coolige Concerts 1940(3)
    - "Puerto Rico Sings 1970"
    - Ribaupierre Quartet, 1926
    - Roth Quartet, 1929
    - Russian Cathedral Choir, 1916
    - Saint John's Episcopal Church, New Haven - piano recital, 1945
    - Samaroff, Olga (piano), 23 Feb 1910
    - Sanford, Samuel - memorial concert, 16 Mar 1910
    - Schroeder, Alwyn (violin), 2 Nov 1909
    - Schubert Centenary, 1928
    - Schumann-Heink, Mme., undated
    - Scotti, Antonio and Bernice de Pasqualis, 1911
    - Segovia, Andres, 1930, 1937, 1938
    - Sembrich, Marcela (soprano), 29 Apr 1910
    - "Serata Musicale Italiana", 1945
    - Shankar, Ravi, 1956, 1961
    - Smallman A Capella Choir, 1929
    - Sousa and His Band, 1910
    - St. Olaf Lutheran Choir, 1929 (2), 1948 (1)
    - Starlight Festival of Chamber Music, 1956 (?) (2), 1962
    - Stojowski, Sigismund and Thadduys Wronski, 1916
    - Theater Integral presents Stravinsky Evening, 1960
    - Twilight Concert, 1965(2)
    - U.S. Marine Band, 1907, 1922(2)
    - University Glee Club of New Haven (see also Yale Glee Club and University Glee Club of New Haven), 1925, 1926, 1927 (3), 1928 (2), 1929 (2)
    - University of Illinois - Collegium Musicum of, 1958
    - University Orchestra, 1952 (2), 1953 (2), 1954 (2), 1955 (2), 1956, 1957
    - Van Buren Players of Ancient Instruments, 1936, 1939
    - Vatican Chorus, 1919
    - Wagner, Richard - 50th Anniversary of the Death of, 1933
    - Wellesley College Orchestra and Yale University Orchestra, 1941, 1942
    - Woolsey Hall Concert Series (Steinert Concerts), 1916 (3), 1917 (3), 1918 (2), 1919 (5), 1920 (6), 1921 (3), 1922 (4), 1919-1920, 1921 (2), 1922 (3), 1923 (6), 1924 (7), 1925 (4), 1926 (4), 1927 (8), 1928 (7), 1929 (2); 1930 (5), 1931 (6), 1932 (6), 1933 (3), 1934 (5), 1935 (4), 1936 (3), 1939 (2), 1940 (3), 1941 (4), 1942 (4), 1943 (6), 1944 (6), 1945 (6), 1946 (8), 1947 (7), 1948 (6), 1949 (7); 1950 (7), 1951 (7), 1952 (7), 1953 (6), 1954 (8), 1955 (7), 1956 (6), 1957 (6), 1958 (8), 1959 (5), 1960 (8), 1961 (6), 1962 (7), 1963 (7), 1964 (7), 1965 (9), 1966 (6), 1967 (6), 1968 (7), 1969 (7), 1970 (4)
    - Woman's Choral Society of New Haven, 1935
    - Yale Chamber Orchestra, 1934
    - Yale Club of New Haven presents Yale University Band, 1959 (2), 1960-1969
    - Yale Faculty Trio, 1907 (3), 1908 (3), 1909 (3), 1910 (4)
    - Yale Gilbert and Sullivan Society, 1965
    - Yale Glee Club and University Glee Club of New Haven, 1890-1899 (6), 1919, 1923 (2), 1926, 1927, 1928 (2), 1931 (2), 1932 (2), 1933 (2), 1934 (3), 1935 (3), 1936 (3), 193 7 (4), 193 8 (4), 193 9 (4), 1940 (4), 1941 (6), 1942 (3), 1943 (4), 1944 (2), 1945 (4); 1946 (3), 1947 (7), 1948 (4), 1949 (5), 1950 (6), 1951 (7), 1952 (5), 1953 (6), 1954 (4), 1955 (6), 1956 (8), 1957 (5), 1958 (4); 1959 (9), 1960 (3), 1961 (6), 1962 (8), 1963 (8), 1964 (10), 1965 (8), 1966 (8), 1967 (7), 1968 (4), 1969 (6), 1970 (4)
    - Yale Memorial Carillon, 1963, 1966(10)
    - Yale Music Association, 1940
    - Yale School of Music Chamber Music Series, 1940 (2), 1941 (5), 1942 (4), 1943 (6), 1944 (5), 1945 (4), 1946 (5), 1947 (6), 1948 (4), 1949 (4), 1950 (5), 1951 (5), 1952 (5), 1953 (5), 1954 (3), 1955 (2), 1956 (1), 1957 (5), 1958 (5), 1959 (3), 1960 (5), 1961 (6), 1962 (6), 1963 (2)
    - Yale School of Music - Recital of Chamber Music, 1926, 1930 (2), 1931 (4), 1932 (4), 1933 (4), 1934 (4), 1935 (5), 1936 (4), 1937 (7), 1938 (3), 1939 (6), 1940 (2), 1940 (2), 1941?
    - "Yale Swings" Jazz Recital, 1957
    - Yale Symphony Orchestra, 1966, 1967, 1968 (4), 1969 (4), 1970 (3)
    - "Yale Symphony Orchestra"/ Yale University Orchestra, 1921, 1922
    - Yale University, 1970
    - Yale University Band, 1947, 1949, 1951-1958, 1960-1968, 1969(2)
    - Yale University Band Pops Concert, 1955, 1956, 1957, 1958
    - Yale University Chamber Concerts, 1888(2), 1889 (5), 1890, 1891 (2), 1893 (7), 1894 (7), 1895 (2), 1896 (5), 1897 (3), 1898 (7), 1899 (2); 1900 (3), 1901 (2), 1902 (3), 1904, 1905 (5), 1906 (3), 1907 (4), 1908 (6), 1909 (9), 1910 (3), 1911 (5-6?), 1912 (3-6?), 1913 (3-5?), 1914 (4-5?); 1915 (4-6?), 1916 (3-5?), 1917 (4-5?), 1918 (6-11?), 1919 (4), 1920 (5-9?), 1921 (5-7?), 1922 (5), 1923 (4); 1924 (5), 1925 (2), 1026 (4), 1927 (2), 1935, 1936 (2), 1951 (2), 1963 (4), 1964 (18), 1965 (22), 1966 (32), 1967 (11), 1968 (19), 1969 (23), 1970 (15)
    - Yale University Department of Music and the Collection of Musical Instruments, undated
    - Yale University School of Drama and School of Music, 1963
    - Yale University School of Music Faculty (Ensemble) Concert, 1956, 1961
    - Yale University Theatre and the Yale School of Music, 1940
    - Ysaye, Eugene, 1913